vikingbags.com 2019-04-10

# Privacy Policy - Vikingbags

We like to make sure that every customer feels the warm and welcomed. Know that we collect information from you when you connect and interact with us, whether it is a one-time question or as a regular buyer. This information helps us retain relevant information about you and thereby serve you better. We understand that many of you are reluctant to give out personal information and we completely respect your wishes. However, if you do wish to do business with us, some information will be required. Please know that you have our 100% assurance that we keep all your information confidential and do not share, sell, or exchange this data with any third party.

## Collection of your Personal Information:

We collect information from our numerous clients in order to; prevent fraud, provide a better shopping experience, provide better customer service, for marketing needs, for legal compliance, and for smooth client-provider transactions. As mentioned, the information is never revealed to third parties and is shared only internally between our various departments to ensure faster and smoother processing of orders. Information is collected online, through surveys, address verification services, and social networks.

Personal information collected can include; name, company or organization name, along with contact details like address, phone, and email. Some records are automatically stored like the type of browser you use, the pages you browsed when you visited our site, the date and time of your last visit, and the IP address. 

## Use of your Personal Information:

We value the trust and faith that you have shown in us. Therefore, the information collected may be used to notify you with critical updates from time to time and help our staff serve your better. Other than that, you can be assured that the confidentiality of your data will be maintained at all times.

## How can we guarantee the security of your data?

Our servers are protected by powerful and secure firewalls and SSL technology, which prevent hacking and easy information access by third party users. This is true not just for storing the data but also for every transaction you make through our site. The SSL encryption, which you can easily see on the URL by “https”. This confirms that our server has a secure connection which protects all sensitive data from being compromised.

We like to make sure that every customer feels the warm and welcomed. Know that we collect information from you when you connect and interact with us, whether it is a one-time question or as a regular buyer. This information helps us retain relevant information about you and thereby serve you better. We understand that many of you are reluctant to give out personal information and we completely respect your wishes. However, if you do wish to do business with us, some information will be required. Please know that you have our 100% assurance that we keep all your information confidential and do not share, sell, or exchange this data with any third party.
